[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "Specifically, apparently, so you can you vote for Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Specifically", ",", "apparently", ",", "so", "you", "can", "you", "vote", "for", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Mickey, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Mickey", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Five-year break.", "answer_tokens": ["Five-year", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "I've always wondered, why would you -- in the middle of this dazzling film career -- want to go and get beaten around the head?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "always", "wondered", ",", "why", "would", "you", "--", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "this", "dazzling", "film", "career", "--", "want", "to", "go", "and", "get", "beaten", "around", "the", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ":", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "The acting wasn't something I was having fun doing anymore or liked doing.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "acting", "was", "n't", "something", "I", "was", "having", "fun", "doing", "anymore", "or", "liked", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "You've always loved boxing, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "always", "loved", "boxing", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "How did it go, the boxing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "it", "go", ",", "the", "boxing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "It went good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "went", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "MD", "VB", ",", "MD", "VB", ",", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Did you ever think you could have been a proper contestant?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "think", "you", "could", "have", "been", "a", "proper", "contestant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "I never say could have, would have, should have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "say", "could", "have", ",", "would", "have", ",", "should", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "But what does it give you, that feeling when you get into the ring?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "does", "it", "give", "you", ",", "that", "feeling", "when", "you", "get", "into", "the", "ring", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "You know what it was, I needed the discipline.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "it", "was", ",", "I", "needed", "the", "discipline", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "And, boy, was it the comeback movie?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "boy", ",", "was", "it", "the", "comeback", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Well, you know, I did the movie at a time when I still wasn't very bankable.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "did", "the", "movie", "at", "a", "time", "when", "I", "still", "was", "n't", "very", "bankable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, you know, the guy did a really great job with the nose.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "guy", "did", "a", "really", "great", "job", "with", "the", "nose", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Is that from the fighting?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "from", "the", "fighting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Well, you know, I always had trouble with wrapping my hands, because my hands would swell up.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "always", "had", "trouble", "with", "wrapping", "my", "hands", ",", "because", "my", "hands", "would", "swell", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Why do you think you did it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "you", "did", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, I did it because I had some issues when I was very young with authority and with physical --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "it", "because", "I", "had", "some", "issues", "when", "I", "was", "very", "young", "with", "authority", "and", "with", "physical", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "In the wilderness years, I mean, when you were walking, say, into a store in Hollywood, a grocery store or something, what was the reality of that?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "wilderness", "years", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "when", "you", "were", "walking", ",", "say", ",", "into", "a", "store", "in", "Hollywood", ",", "a", "grocery", "store", "or", "something", ",", "what", "was", "the", "reality", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "It was terrible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "terrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "You actually hear that line?", "question_tokens": ["You", "actually", "hear", "that", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Oh, yes, didn't you used to be.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "used", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "ORGAN: What was the worst name?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "was", "the", "worst", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "I'm not going to go there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "go", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stallone"]}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Who were the guys, the other actors who really stuck by you?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "were", "the", "guys", ",", "the", "other", "actors", "who", "really", "stuck", "by", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Well, Stallone helped me out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Stallone", "helped", "me", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Had you seen each other since?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "you", "seen", "each", "other", "since", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Once.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "When you met up again this time, how did it go?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "met", "up", "again", "this", "time", ",", "how", "did", "it", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "It's always nerve-racking.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "always", "nerve-racking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Or was it weary?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "it", "weary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, the first time we saw each in over 20 years was last year or something.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "time", "we", "saw", "each", "in", "over", "20", "years", "was", "last", "year", "or", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "What was your view of the book?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "view", "of", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I don't have any desire to read it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "desire", "to", "read", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Anyway, what's the next thing you want to talk about?", "question_tokens": ["Anyway", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "next", "thing", "you", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "No, but I -- I mean, it's fascinating, because I have discussed this with you before.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "fascinating", ",", "because", "I", "have", "discussed", "this", "with", "you", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Do you ever wonder about that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "wonder", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "No, I don't have to wonder.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "wonder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mickey"]}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "You feel me?", "question_tokens": ["You", "feel", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "I think I'm feeling you, Mickey.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'m", "feeling", "you", ",", "Mickey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Do you understand them better?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "them", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "No, they're stronger than us.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "'re", "stronger", "than", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Hey, listen, it would be a really terrible place if it was just me, you and these camera guys, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "listen", ",", "it", "would", "be", "a", "really", "terrible", "place", "if", "it", "was", "just", "me", ",", "you", "and", "these", "camera", "guys", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "It would be a terrible place.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "a", "terrible", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "TO", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Are an easier guy to go out with, to date, to be with?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "an", "easier", "guy", "to", "go", "out", "with", ",", "to", "date", ",", "to", "be", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", ",", "TO", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "No, I'm -- to date, not necessarily, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "--", "to", "date", ",", "not", "necessarily", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Is that the ultimate?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "ultimate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Listen, when I -- listen, just to get the second chance, they're letting me back in the door.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "when", "I", "--", "listen", ",", "just", "to", "get", "the", "second", "chance", ",", "they", "'re", "letting", "me", "back", "in", "the", "door", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Do you still feel that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "feel", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Do you still drink much?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "drink", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "It wasn't the drinking.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "n't", "the", "drinking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What was your problem?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "My anger.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "anger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "And does that still flare up?", "question_tokens": ["And", "does", "that", "still", "flare", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Does he know he butchered my mother?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "know", "he", "butchered", "my", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Now that he has seen your face, he knows.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "that", "he", "has", "seen", "your", "face", ",", "he", "knows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "He came out to your premier last week?", "question_tokens": ["He", "came", "out", "to", "your", "premier", "last", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "OURKE: Yes, he did.", "answer_tokens": ["OURKE", ":", "Yes", ",", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Who told you?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "told", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "You told me.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "told", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "What do you make of what's happening with your country right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "happening", "with", "your", "country", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "I have -- I like the way you say with your country.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "--", "I", "like", "the", "way", "you", "say", "with", "your", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CD", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "What is going wrong with America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "wrong", "with", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I don't really have one, to be honest with you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "really", "have", "one", ",", "to", "be", "honest", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Are you learning a bit of diplomatic tact in your old age, Mickey?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "learning", "a", "bit", "of", "diplomatic", "tact", "in", "your", "old", "age", ",", "Mickey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mickey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Do you think actors should spout off about politics?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "actors", "should", "spout", "off", "about", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I'll let you read my mind.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "let", "you", "read", "my", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "There's a wild rumor you got engaged recently?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "wild", "rumor", "you", "got", "engaged", "recently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "No, I didn't get engaged.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "get", "engaged", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Are you with anyone in any sort of serious way?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "with", "anyone", "in", "any", "sort", "of", "serious", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "None of your business, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "of", "your", "business", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "You're quite bossy, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "quite", "bossy", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Do you always get your own way?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "always", "get", "your", "own", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "But you see, you did it.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "you", "see", ",", "you", "did", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "I mean, you boss him around?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "boss", "him", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "He's big, but he's very gentle.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "big", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "very", "gentle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have met Seal?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "to", "have", "met", "Seal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Because it felt like the pair of you had been sort of searching for each other and then you collided, and you have this extraordinary life with hundreds of children and fabulously successful careers?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "felt", "like", "the", "pair", "of", "you", "had", "been", "sort", "of", "searching", "for", "each", "other", "and", "then", "you", "collided", ",", "and", "you", "have", "this", "extraordinary", "life", "with", "hundreds", "of", "children", "and", "fabulously", "successful", "careers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Four.", "answer_tokens": ["Four", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Was it really?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "What were you both doing there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "both", "doing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "I was just visiting a friend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "just", "visiting", "a", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "You knew him, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "knew", "him", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I hadn't met him before.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "n't", "met", "him", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "So what happened then?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "happened", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Then we met each other again, but always with friends.", "answer_tokens": ["Then", "we", "met", "each", "other", "again", ",", "but", "always", "with", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Do you want to go through it again (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "go", "through", "it", "again", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "It went like this and normally we'd go and we just went like this.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "went", "like", "this", "and", "normally", "we", "'d", "go", "and", "we", "just", "went", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "And who gripped who?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "gripped", "who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "We both gripped each other.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "both", "gripped", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "And what were you thinking in that second?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "in", "that", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I got really hot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "really", "hot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Did you think this is the guy?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "this", "is", "the", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "I was like, oh, wow.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "like", ",", "oh", ",", "wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Had you kissed lots of frogs to get to this point?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "you", "kissed", "lots", "of", "frogs", "to", "get", "to", "this", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Otherwise, things just don't get done, do they?", "question_tokens": ["Otherwise", ",", "things", "just", "do", "n't", "get", "done", ",", "do", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "So you squeeze hands, and then you get married.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "you", "squeeze", "hands", ",", "and", "then", "you", "get", "married", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "He had an igloo built on a mountain?", "question_tokens": ["He", "had", "an", "igloo", "built", "on", "a", "mountain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 596, "question": "And what were his exact words of proposal?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "were", "his", "exact", "words", "of", "proposal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "\"Do you want to marry me?\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Do", "you", "want", "to", "marry", "me", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "What did you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "I said yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Henry"]}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "ORGAN: And then what happened?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "And", "then", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "And then nine months later Henry was born.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "then", "nine", "months", "later", "Henry", "was", "born", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "How do you be a mother to four children with everything else you do?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "be", "a", "mother", "to", "four", "children", "with", "everything", "else", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "You know, I don't know how that happened.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "that", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Are there any more planned?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "any", "more", "planned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "RBR", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "No, that's it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Do you like working with him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "working", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "How do you keep this skinny figure that you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "keep", "this", "skinny", "figure", "that", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you started it there would be nine seasons?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "when", "you", "started", "it", "there", "would", "be", "nine", "seasons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "No way.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "-- right?", "question_tokens": ["--", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Did I pronounce that right?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "I", "pronounce", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "Was that always the dream for you?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "always", "the", "dream", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "You conquered the world of modeling, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "conquered", "the", "world", "of", "modeling", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "A little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 770, "question": "Not thin enough and too short?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "thin", "enough", "and", "too", "short", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 771, "answer": "For this industry, yes, because the designers such as him, they require the girls to be a certain weight, height and size.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "this", "industry", ",", "yes", ",", "because", "the", "designers", "such", "as", "him", ",", "they", "require", "the", "girls", "to", "be", "a", "certain", "weight", ",", "height", "and", "size", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 773, "question": "And, also, it's dangerous sort of nonsense that he's spouting, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "also", ",", "it", "'s", "dangerous", "sort", "of", "nonsense", "that", "he", "'s", "spouting", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "I mean, I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 781, "question": "If I don't, I go back to Germany and I do something else, you know?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "do", "n't", ",", "I", "go", "back", "to", "Germany", "and", "I", "do", "something", "else", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "I mean, there is a danger --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "there", "is", "a", "danger", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "Any -- any scalpel at any stage?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "--", "any", "scalpel", "at", "any", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 817, "question": "Would you ever?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "ever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 818, "answer": "I mean, I don't want to say never.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "say", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "You like making money, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "like", "making", "money", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "That, too.", "answer_tokens": ["That", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "Where did you get that from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "get", "that", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "I don't know if I'm that smart at it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "'m", "that", "smart", "at", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 871, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 872, "answer": "That's true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'94"]}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "-- keen to do that?", "question_tokens": ["--", "keen", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "I've been here since '94.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "here", "since", "'94", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 880, "question": "What do you think of America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 881, "answer": "I really like it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "In the modern era, in the last sort of 30, 40 years?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "modern", "era", ",", "in", "the", "last", "sort", "of", "30", ",", "40", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "In Germany, definitely, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "Germany", ",", "definitely", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 914, "question": "What's next for the Heidi Klum Incorporated machine?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "next", "for", "the", "Heidi", "Klum", "Incorporated", "machine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 915, "answer": "More designing.", "answer_tokens": ["More", "designing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi Klum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 920, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 921, "answer": "From the things -- yes, that I cook up.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "the", "things", "--", "yes", ",", "that", "I", "cook", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 934, "question": "-- to, any of them, to get into fashion, would you worry about it, given the experiences you've had?", "question_tokens": ["--", "to", ",", "any", "of", "them", ",", "to", "get", "into", "fashion", ",", "would", "you", "worry", "about", "it", ",", "given", "the", "experiences", "you", "'ve", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 935, "answer": "I would not push them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "not", "push", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 943, "question": "-- a rock star like their dad?", "question_tokens": ["--", "a", "rock", "star", "like", "their", "dad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 944, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 954, "question": "Well I -- I look forward to these kids growing up, actually, because they must -- they're going to look great and be very talented, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "I", "--", "I", "look", "forward", "to", "these", "kids", "growing", "up", ",", "actually", ",", "because", "they", "must", "--", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "look", "great", "and", "be", "very", "talented", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 955, "answer": "Oh, they're a lot of fun.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "they", "'re", "a", "lot", "of", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 960, "question": "What's your proudest achievement, you personally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "proudest", "achievement", ",", "you", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 961, "answer": "Oh, my family for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "family", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 968, "question": "And then what?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 969, "answer": "And you come home to a guy who just gets on bended knee in igloos and sings you crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "you", "come", "home", "to", "a", "guy", "who", "just", "gets", "on", "bended", "knee", "in", "igloos", "and", "sings", "you", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]